<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
<title type="text">Workshop in the Woods: Audio Visual Synthesis</title>
<generator uri="https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll">Jekyll</generator>
<link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" />
<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://localhost:4000" />
<updated>2014-08-21T12:28:29-04:00</updated>
<id>http://localhost:4000/</id>
<author>
  <name>Bregman Music Audio Research Studio</name>
  <uri>http://localhost:4000/</uri>
  <email>sarroff@cs.dartmouth.edu</email>
</author>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[About the Workshop]]></title>
 <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://localhost:4000/sticky/about/" />
  <id>http://localhost:4000/sticky/about</id>
  <published>2014-08-21T00:00:00-04:00</published>
  <updated>2014-08-21T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Bregman Music Audio Research Studio</name>
    <uri>http://localhost:4000</uri>
    <email>sarroff@cs.dartmouth.edu</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;basics&quot;&gt;Basics&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Digital Musics graduate program of the Dartmouth College Music Department is hosting a three day workshop from &lt;strong&gt;October 10 to October 12&lt;/strong&gt; in rural New Hampshire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;details&quot;&gt;Details&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This workshop brings together &lt;strong&gt;creative computer scientists, programmers, musicians, and visual artists&lt;/strong&gt; for a three day workshop on audio and visual synthesis methods. The workshop is located in a remote pastoral setting where the participants will have free reign to roam the grounds, take hikes, and gather by a campfire at night. During the days the workshop will include tutorials, a poster session, and roundtable discussions. The evenings will include performances by invited multimedia artists and collective &lt;em&gt;AV synthesis jams&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We invite anyone with research interest in creative applications for audio or visual synthesis to register. The following topics will be included in the workshop (among others):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Brain-media mappings&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Neural net based synthesizers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Physical modeling&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Parametric models&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Data driven synthesis models and machine learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Delicious meals and snacks will be catered by the inn. Lodging for 2 evenings will be provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;participate&quot;&gt;Participate&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If interested please &lt;strong&gt;register&lt;/strong&gt; with us. After that, go to the &lt;strong&gt;wiki&lt;/strong&gt; and create a page explaining a little bit about yourself. If you have any questions &lt;strong&gt;contact us&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to limited resources we require all attendees to participate fully in the event. If you are not sure that you can commit to the full weekend, please do not register. Contact us and explain your situation. If we can accommodate you we’ll let you know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-success&quot;&gt;Register&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-info&quot;&gt;Wiki&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:sarroff@cs.dartmouth.edu&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-primary&quot;&gt;Contact Us&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/sticky/about/&quot;&gt;About the Workshop&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Bregman Music Audio Research Studio at &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000&quot;&gt;Workshop in the Woods: Audio Visual Synthesis&lt;/a&gt; on August 21, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>

</feed>
